<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="key_description">Create narratives about any subject</string>
    <string name="key_search">Search</string>
    <string name="key_try">Try</string>
    <string name="key_teste">something</string>
    <string name="key_options">
        <u>Advanced Options</u>
    </string>
    <string name="lingua">Português</string>
    <string name="key_title">tell me stories</string>
    <string name="know_team">know the team</string>
    <string name="exemplos1">Economy and Society</string>
    <string name="exemplos2">" Politics, Justice and Journalism"</string>
    <string name="exemplos3">Sports and Culture</string>
    <string name="sobre">about</string>
    <string name="pesquisar">Search</string>
    <string name="what_is">What\'s Tell me stories?</string>
    <string name="menu_exemplos">Examples</string>
    <string name="menu_pesquisar">Search</string>
    <string name="menu_sobre">About</string>
    <string name="menu_equipa">Team</string>

    <string name="sobreConta">Tell me Stories</string>

    <string name="sobreContaT">
        &lt;a href="http://tellmestories.pt">Tell me Stories&lt;/a> <a>is a temporal summarization framework of news
        articles that allows
        users to explore and revisit events in the past. Built on top of the
    </a> &lt;a href="http://arquivo.pt">Portuguese web archive&lt;/a><a>,</a>
        <a> it can be extended to support different datasets, including traditional media such as Reuters, Bloomberg, etc.</a>
    </string>
    <string name="sobreFunciona">How does it work?</string>
    <string name="sobreFuncionaT">
        <a>Tell me Stories collects information from web archives (such as the Arquivo.pt) or media
            outlets (such as Reuters, Bloomberg or Bing News) and provides a full-text search service that enables the
            retrieval of past (to present) information. To select relevant stories of different time-periods, we rely on
        </a> &lt;a href="http://yake.inesctec.pt">YAKE!&lt;/a>
        <a>a keyword extraction algorithm developed by our research team, which selects the
            most important excerpts (namely text titles) of a topic over time, to present to the user.
        </a>
    </string>
    <string name="sobreContribuicoes">Contributions</string>
    <string name="sobreContribuicoesT">"During the last decade, we have been witnessing an ever-growing number of online
        contents posing new challenges for those who aim to understand a given event. This exponential growth of the
        volume of data, together with the phenomenon of media bias, fake news and filter bubbles, has contributed to the
        creation of new challenges in information access and transparency."&lt;br/>
    </string>
    <string name="sobreSoftwareT">

        <a>Tell me Stories is available at</a> &lt;a
        href="https://play.google.com/store/apps">Google Play&lt;/a><a>,</a>  &lt;a
        href="http://tellmestories.pt">online&lt;/a> <a>
        and on
    </a> &lt;a
        href="https://github.com/LIAAD/TemporalSummarizationFramework">Github&lt;/a>
        <a>through which we make available a Python package that can be extended to support different datasets or languages.</a>
    </string>
    <string name="sobrePremios">Awards</string>
    <string name="sobrePremiosT">
        <a>Winner of the</a> &lt;a
        href="https://sobre.arquivo.pt/en/arquivo-pt-2018-award-winners/">Arquivo.pt 2018 contest&lt;/a>
        <a>and of the Best Demo Presentation at the 41st  European Conference on Information Retrieval (</a>
       &lt;a href="http://www.ecir2019.org"> ECIR’19&lt;/a> <a>).</a>
    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferenciasT01">Tell me Stories is a research product. If you use it in a work that leads to a
        scientific publication, research project or product, please cite the following references:&lt;br/>&lt;br/>

    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferenciasT02"><a>Campos, R., Pasquali, A., Jatowt, A., Mangaravite, V., and Jorge, A. (2020).</a>
        <a>Automatic generation of timelines for past events</a><a>. In Gomes, D., et al. (Eds.), The Past Web: exploring web
        archives. Springer Book. To appear.</a> &lt;br/>&lt;br/>
    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferenciasT03">Pasquali, A., Mangaravite, V., Campos, R., Jorge, A., and Jatowt, A. (2019).
        &lt;a href=" https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-030-15719-7_34">Interactive System for Automatically Generating Temporal Narratives&lt;/a>. In Azzopardi et al. (Eds.), Lecture Notes
        in Computer Science - Advances in Information Retrieval - 41st European Conference on Information Retrieval
        (ECIR\'19). Cologne, Germany. April 14 – 18. (Vol. 11438 (2019), pp. 251 - 255) &lt;br/>
    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferencias">References</string>
    <string name="sobreContribuicoesT02">One possible approach to overcome this problem is to automatically summarize
        large amount of news into consistent narratives. Tell me Stories emerges in this context, as an important
        contribution for anyone interested in having access to the overall picture of a given event in a quick manner.
        Our project may be considered as an additional solution that allows the general public (students, journalists,
        politics, researchers, etc) to better explore any kind of data that has been covered by the media.
    </string>
    <string name="equipaTexto">This project was developed by researchers affiliated to the Polytechnic Institute of Tomar,
        LIAAD INESC TEC, University of Porto and University of Kyoto. \n
    </string>
    <string name="agradecimentos">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="institui_es">Institutions</string>
    <string name="instituicao_texto">Colocarem os logotipos das instituições envolvidas (podem vê-los no sobre….no fundo
        da página). Coloquem todos menos o último (o four eyes). Esse é para ser colocado no item a seguir
    </string>
    <string name="financiamento">Funding</string>
    <string name="financiamento_texto">This project was partially funded by Project “TEC4Growth - Pervasive
        Intelligence, Enhancers and Proofs of Concept with Industrial Impact/NORTE-01-0145-FEDER-000020” which is
        financed by the NORTE 2020, under the PORTUGAL 2020 Partnership Agreement, and through the European Regional
        Development Fund (ERDF).
    </string>
    <string name="outros">Others</string>
    <string name="outros_texto">
        A special thanks goes to the <a href="http://arquivo.pt">Portuguese Web Archive</a> and to its team for creating an
        outstanding platform that aims to archive the Portuguese digital contents, thus providing not only the share of
        knowledge but also the emergence of new and innovative products.

    </string>
    <string name="creditos_texto">Tell me Stories app has been developed by Simão Samouco and João Campos under the
        supervision of Professor Ricardo Campos in the scope of the Final Project of the Computer Science degree of the
        Polytechnic Institute of Tomar, Portugal.
    </string>
    <string name="creditos">Credits</string>
    <string name="contactos">contact</string>
    <string name="contactos_texto">For any inquires please contact us at:</string>
    <string name="contactos_menu">Contacts</string>
    <string name="cargo_resea_prof">PROFESSOR AND RESEARCHER</string>
    <string name="cargo_soft_resea">SOFTWARE DEVELOPER AND RESEARCHER</string>
    <string name="cargo_commuticaions">COMMUNICATIONS</string>
    <string name="mobile_developer">MOBILE DEVELOPER</string>
    <string name="creditos_frag">credits</string>
    <string name="copiar_mail">Copy Mail</string>
    <string name="liaad_url">https://www.inesctec.pt/en</string>
    <string name="search_box">Search</string>
    <string name="five_years">Last 5 years</string>
    <string name="ten_years">Last 10 years</string>
    <string name="fifteen_years">Last 15 years</string>
    <string name="twenty_years">Last 20 years</string>
    <string-array name="country_arrays">
        <item>Last 5 years</item>
        <item>Last 10 years</item>
        <item>Last 15 years</item>
        <item>Last 20 years</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="origem_nome">esconder</string>
    <string name="mail_foi_copiado">" Mail has been copied"</string>
    <string name="loading_wordcloud">The Wordcloud is loading...</string>
    <string name="helpere">
        <string name="link">&lt;a href="http://www.google.com">Google&lt;/a></string>
    </string>
    <string name="narrativa">Narrative</string>
    <string name="termos_relacionas">Word Cloud</string>
    <string name="error_main_text">System is currently busy</string>
    <string name="error_text_secondary">We are currently working on that and hope its temporary. \n Please try again later
    </string>
    <string name="button_voltar">back to beginning</string>
    <string name="key_media_title">Institutions</string>
</resources>
