<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="key_description">Create narratives about any subject</string>
    <string name="key_search">Search</string>
    <string name="key_try">Try</string>
    <string name="key_teste">something</string>
    <string name="key_options">
        <u>Advanced Options</u>
    </string>
    <string name="lingua">Português</string>
    <string name="key_title" >tell me stories</string>
    <string name="know_team">know the team</string>
    <string name="exemplos1">Economy and Present</string>
    <string name="exemplos2">" Politics, Justice and Journalism"</string>
    <string name="exemplos3">Sports and Culture</string>
    <string name="sobre">about</string>
    <string name="pesquisar">Search</string>
    <string name="what_is">What\'s Tell me stories?</string>
    <string name="menu_exemplos">Examples</string>
    <string name="menu_pesquisar">Search</string>
    <string name="menu_sobre">About</string>
    <string name="menu_equipa">Team</string>

    <string name="sobreConta">Tell me Stories</string>

    <string name="sobreContaT">"Tell me Stories [http://tellmestories.pt] is a temporal summarization framework of news articles that allows users to explore and revisit events in the past. Initially built on top of the Portuguese web archive [http://arquivo.pt], Tell me Stories has been later extended to support different datasets such as Reuters, Bloomberg, Bing or the Signal Media dataset."
    </string>
    <string name="sobreFunciona">How does it work?</string>
    <string name="sobreFuncionaT">Tell me Stories collects information from web archives (such as the Arquivo.pt) or media
        outlets (such as Reuters, Bloomberg or Bing News) and provides a full-text search service that enables the
        retrieval of past (to present) information. To select relevant stories of different time-periods, we rely on
        YAKE! [http://yake.inesctec.pt] a keyword extraction algorithm developed by our research team, which selects the
        most important excerpts (namely text titles) of a topic over time, to present to the user.
    </string>
    <string name="sobreContribuicoes">Contributions</string>
    <string name="sobreContribuicoesT">"During the last decade, we have been witnessing an ever-growing number of online contents posing new challenges for those who aim to understand a given event. This exponential growth of the volume of data, together with the phenomenon of media bias, fake news and filter bubbles, has contributed to the creation of new challenges in information access and transparency."
    </string>
    <string name="sobreSoftwareT">"Tell me Stories is available on Google Play [link do Google Play], online [http://tellmestories.pt] and as an open source Python package [https://github.com/LIAAD/TemporalSummarizationFramework] that can be extended to support different datasets or languages. "
    </string>
    <string name="sobrePremios">Awards</string>
    <string name="sobrePremiosT">Conta-me Histórias / Tell me Stories won the Arquivo.pt 2018 contest [https://sobre.arquivo.pt/en/arquivo-pt-2018-award-winners/] and has been awarded the Best Demo Presentation at ECIR’19 [http://www.ecir2019.org].
    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferenciasT01">Tell me Stories is a research product. If you use it in a work that leads to a
        scientific publication, research project or product, please cite the following references: \n
    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferenciasT02">Campos, R., Pasquali, A., Mangaravite, V., Jorge, A., and Jatowt, A. (2020).
        Automatic generation of timelines for past events. In Gomes, D., et al. (Eds.), The Past Web: exploring web
        archives. Springer Book. \n
    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferenciasT03">Pasquali, A., Mangaravite, V., Campos, R., Jorge, A., and Jatowt, A. (2019).
        Interactive System for Automatically Generating Temporal Narratives. In Azzopardi et al. (Eds.), Lecture Notes
        in Computer Science - Advances in Information Retrieval - 41st European Conference on Information Retrieval
        (ECIR\'19). Cologne, Germany. April 14 – 18. (Vol. 11438 (2019), pp. 251 - 255) \n
    </string>
    <string name="sobreReferencias">References</string>
    <string name="sobreContribuicoesT02">One possible approach to overcome this problem is to automatically summarize large amount of news into consistent narratives. Tell me Stories emerges in this context, as an important contribution for anyone interested in having access to the overall picture of a given event in a quick manner. Our project may be considered as an additional solution that allows the general public (students, journalists, politics, researchers, etc) to better explore any kind of data that has been covered by the media. \n
    </string>
    <string name="equipaTexto">This project was developed by researchers affiliated to Polytechnic Institute of Tomar,
        LIAAD INESC TEC, University of Porto and University of Kyoto. \n
    </string>
    <string name="agradecimentos">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="institui_es">Institutions</string>
    <string name="instituicao_texto">Colocarem os logotipos das instituições envolvidas (podem vê-los no sobre….no fundo
        da página). Coloquem todos menos o último (o four eyes). Esse é para ser colocado no item a seguir
    </string>
    <string name="financiamento">Funding</string>
    <string name="financiamento_texto">This project was partially funded by Project “TEC4Growth - Pervasive
        Intelligence, Enhancers and Proofs of Concept with Industrial Impact/NORTE-01-0145-FEDER-000020” which is
        financed by the NORTE 2020, under the PORTUGAL 2020 Partnership Agreement, and through the European Regional
        Development Fund (ERDF).
    </string>
    <string name="outros">Others</string>
    <string name="outros_texto">A special thanks goes to the Portuguese Web Archive [http://arquivo.pt] and to its team
        for creating an outstanding platform in the purpose of archiving the Portuguese digital contents, through which
        promote the knowledge sharing and the emergence of new and innovative products.\nAlso thanks to Signal Media for the Signal Media 1M articles news dataset, Reuters, Blomberg and Bing for their APIs
    </string>
</resources>
